https://www.harriscomm.com/privacy

Harris Communications | Deaf, Hard of Hearing and Hearing Loss Products
Search:
Equipment
ADA ComplianceAlerting & Notification SystemsAlerting ManufacturersBusiness Office SolutionsClocks, Watches, TimersEmergency ProductsHearing Aid AccessoriesHearing ProtectionLarge Area FM & Infrared SystemsLoop Systems & ReceiversLow VisionCell Phone AccessoriesPersonal AmplifiersSpeech AssistanceStethoscopesTelephonesTinnitus MaskersTV Listening Amplifiers
Books & Multimedia
Baby Sign LanguageChildren's MaterialsSign EnhancersCochlear ImplantsCODA AuthorsConsumer EducationDeaf Author CornerDeaf CultureEntertainmentHard of Hearing AuthorsHearing Loss ResourcesHomeschoolingInterpretingKids ProductsParent's ResourcesReligionSign LanguageSign Language DictionariesTeachingPublic Performance Titles
Gifts & Novelties
Arts & CraftsBagsCups & DrinkwareFlash CardsFloor RugsGames & ToysGift CertificatesGreeting CardsJewelryKeychainsOrnamentsParty FavorsPosters & PlacematsReading & Writing
Sale/Clearance
EquipmentBooks and MediaNovelties
Customer Service
Phone, Orders & ReturnsFAQs/Help for ShoppingFAQs/Help for ProductsResource ArticlesSpeak & Read CallsTradeshows & Donations
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Harris Communications Privacy & Security Policy
Personal Information Collected
Cookies
Sharing of Information
Information Security
Accessible Information
Choices You Have
Children
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
Harris Communications knows that you care how information about you is used when shopping online. This notice describes the Harris Communications privacy policy. Visiting and shopping on www.harriscomm.com and the website of any Harris Communications division indicates your acceptance of the practices in this privacy policy.
Personal Information Collected
The information we learn from customers helps us to personalize your online shopping experience with us. Following are the types of information we gather.
- Information
you provide us
We receive and store any information you provide to us via our webstore
or in any other way. For example, you provide information when you search
for a product, create an account, place an order, request a catalog or catalogs, ask to
be notified on changes to products, provide information in your account
(and you might have more than one if you have used multiple email addresses
when shopping with us), subscribe to newsletters, communicate with us via email, phone, live chat or otherwise,
or share information about a product with others. As a result of these actions, you might provide
us with information such as your name, address, phone numbers, age, gender, product interests and categories, credit
card information, people to whom purchases have been shipped (including
addresses and phone numbers), email addresses of people, and emails sent to us.
You may choose not to provide certain information, but then you might
not be able to take advantage of many of the features found on our webstore.
We use the information that you provide for purposes such as responding
to your requests and questions, customizing your future shopping experience,
and communicating with you.
We sometimes use third party software in order to provide a better user experience on the website.
We allow third-party companies, including Google Analytics Demographics and Interests Reporting, to collect anonymous, non-identifiable data about your visit via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation, when you visit our website.
We use SITEAPPS, which collects anonymous traffic data and all other information useful for SITEAPPS through cookies. SITEAPPS has a non-disclosure policy, specifying that the user may opt for not authorizing the use of its information. To execute the OPT-OUT process, go to http://siteapps.com/web/optout.
- Automatic information
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact
with us. For example, like many other websites, we use "cookies"
which obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses
our website. Examples of information we collect and analyze include
the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to
the Internet; login name/email address; computer and connection
information such as browser type and version, operating system, language, time zone and
computer platform; purchase history (sometimes used to create our Bestseller items
list); the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and
from our webstore, including date and time; cookie number; products
viewed or searched for, clicks and mouse movements, scroll events and keystrokes (keystrokes from password fields or marked as "sensitive" are not tracked or stored). Some user sessions may be recorded.
Visit the Federal Trade Commission's website for more information about online
privacy.
- Email communications
To help us make emails more useful, Harris Communications may receive
confirmation when you open an online account with us.
You may opt-in to receive our email newsletter. Your information will not be sold or leased to another company, but may be shared with third parties in order to promote Harris Communications products. For example, we use a third party re-mailer to distribute our email newsletters on our behalf. If you no longer wish to receive the newsletter, you may UNSUBSCRIBE by following the directions at the bottom of the email newsletter and you will be removed from the email list.
- Information from other sources
We might receive information about you from other sources and add it
to our account information. Examples include updated delivery and address
information from our shipping carriers or other third parties, which
we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication;
account information, purchase or redemption information; search term
and search result information from Internet search engines; and credit
history information from credit bureaus which we use to help detect
and prevent fraud and to offer certain credit or financial services
to some customers.
Cookies
- Cookies
are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's
hard drive through your web browser. They enable our systems to recognize
your browser and to provide features such as the storage or transfer
of items added your shopping cart between visits or before account login.
- The Help portion of the toolbar on most web browsers provide information on how
to prevent your browser from accepting cookies, how to have the browser
notify you before receiving a new cookie, or how to disable your browser
from accepting any cookies. However, cookies allow you to take full
advantage of some of the features on our website, and we recommend that
you leave them turned on.
Sharing of Information
Harris Communications does not sell or lease information about our customers to others.
Information Security
- We work to protect the security of your information during transmission with
Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information
you input.
- Your credit card number is not transmitted in any emails transmitted
to you when confirming an order. We do not save credit card numbers on our webstore. In addition, once orders have been
processed, credit card numbers are deleted from our online computer systems.
- You can protect yourself against unauthorized use of your account
information by signing off when you have finished your order or after using
a shared computer.
Links
This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Accessible Information
Harris Communications gives you access to a wide range of information about your
account for the limited purpose of viewing and/or updating that information.
Examples of information you can easily access include information regarding
recent orders; personal information (including name, email address, password,
communications preferences, address book, product notification settings);
email notification settings; and recommendations (including purchase history). Of course the list may change as our webstore evolves.
Choices You Have
- As mentioned above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though
it may be required to make a purchase or to use features on the webstore.
- You can add or update certain information such as those listed in
the Accessible information section above.
- The Help portion of the toolbar on most web browsers provide information
on how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies, how to have the
browser notify you before receiving a new cookie, or how to disable
your browser from accepting any cookies. However, cookies allow you
to take full advantage of some of the features on our website, and we
recommend that you leave them turned on.
- Visit the Federal Trade Commission's website for more information
about online privacy.
Children
Harris Communications does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell
children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18 years
of age, you may use the Harris Communications website with the involvement
of a parent or guardian only.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to use one of the Harris Communications website, your visit
and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Conditions
of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and
application of the law of the state of Minnesota. Read our entire Conditions of Use. If you have any concerns
about privacy at Harris Communications, please send a thorough description
to info@harriscomm.com and we
will try to resolve it.
Our business is changing constantly, and our Privacy Policy and Conditions
of Use may also change. We may email periodic reminders of our notices
and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should also
check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless otherwise stated,
our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about
you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and
will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less
protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent
of affected customers.
© 2018 Harris Communications, Inc. All Rights Reserved. | 15155 Technology Dr, Eden Prairie MN 55344
Voice: (800) 825-6758 / TTY: (800) 825-9187 / Fax: (952) 906-1099 / VP: (952) 388-2152
